Darren Victoriano

Software Developer Engineer in Test

About Me

Adaptable professional with years of experience and a proven knowledge of test automation, quality assurance and full-stack web development. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the SDET role at your company.

Contact

- San Diego, CA
- darren.victoriano@gmail.com
- https://darrenvictoriano.herokuapp.com
- www.github.com/darrenvictoriano
- in www.linkedin.com/in/darren-victoriano

Skills

Python



Java



JavaScript (Node.js & React.js)



MongoDB / MySQL



Robot Framework / Selenium



GCP / Kubernates / GCloud



Experience

Sr. Software Test Engineer at Dexcom

January 2021 – Present

- Develops test automation framework using Python and Robot Framework. Testing Dexcom's backend code and API endpoints.
- Develops automation scripts and tools to help and support the creation of supporting test documents like test matrix, software requirements matrix and other tool as needed.
- Help support my team as a test lead to manage our task priority, test schedule and tech debt. I also onboard and train newly hired engineer that joined our team.

Software Test Engineer at Sony Electronics

January 2016 - January 2021

- Develops automation framework for Android TVs and Android Apps using Python, Windows Batch, Linux Bash, Android Debug Tools and/or other tools/programming language if necessary.
- Test Sony's API using either Node.js with Mocha and Chai framework or Java with TestNG or JUnit. Test Web App using Selenium or Android App using Appium.
- Test consumer electronic products and technology such as HDMI2.1 Specification (eARC. VRR, ALLM), Modern TV audio and display specification (HDR, Dolby Vision, Dolby Atmos)

Projects

atvAudit

github.com/DarrenVictoriano/atvAudit

 A full-stack web application that scans an Android device and records all packages and apps that are currently installed while showing all application/s that had an update.

atvAuto

github.com/DarrenVictoriano/atvAuto

 This is an Android TV automation framework, this tool mimick the functionality of the TV's remote control by sending IR command directly to the TV via ADB shell using IP control.

Education

Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

UCSD-Extension, San Diego, CA 2018-2019

Certified Software Tester

Escondido Adult School, Escondido, CA 2014-2015

Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science

AMA University, Philippines 2009-2013